{
  "QuestionModels": [
    {
      "Question": "Choose the sentence that contains the most logical word order.",
      "Answer": "Do you want me to put the book away?"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Choose the sentence that contains the most logical word order.",
      "Answer": "John put the dishes in the sink."
    },
    {
      "Question": "Jane: \"What ________?\" Mary: \"I'm trying to fix my calculator.\"",
      "Answer": "are you doing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Whattime ________?",
      "Answer": "doesthetrainleave?"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I do have a bit of a sweet tooth. I still take three _________ of sugar in my coffee.",
      "Answer": "spoons"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The receptionist at the front desk gave me two ___________.",
      "Answer": "piecesofinformation"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My cousin is very beautiful. She has green eyes and _________ .",
      "Answer": "longhair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can I borrow _________from you? I've left mine at home and I want to write some notes.",
      "Answer": "a pieceofpaper"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the plural form of fish?",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the plural form of wolf?",
      "Answer": "wolves"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I didn't buy ______ in the end.",
      "Answer": "anything"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He was an only child, so he had to learn how to amuse _______.",
      "Answer": "himself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Despite her father's complaints, she decided to live _______ in Canada.",
      "Answer": "byherself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A student of ________ has just been to see me.",
      "Answer": "yours"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Her parents were in Malaya. So were _________.",
      "Answer": "mine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Carlos is an excellent student. He _________ goes to class.",
      "Answer": "always"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Dotheyplay________?",
      "Answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ben and Deny are very similar. ______ is good at football, but they both love watching it on TV.",
      "Answer": "Neither of them"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sitting at a computer all day can be very _________.",
      "Answer": "tiring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The movie was so ___________ that we couldn‟t't sleep at night.",
      "Answer": "exciting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I only want ______ sugar in my tea, please.",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The interesting thing about ______ is all the roads they built in Britain.",
      "Answer": "the Romans"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ President of the United States will be visiting Australia next week.",
      "Answer": "The"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What do you usually have for _______ breakfast?",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Paris is _____ capital of France.",
      "Answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is the bank _______ to the library?",
      "Answer": "next"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It's a small town in the south _____ England.",
      "Answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Bad weather prevented the match ______ going ahead.",
      "Answer": "from"
    },
    {
      "Question": "William is very excited ______ starting his new job.",
      "Answer": "about"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You have to leave your shoes ______________the door when you enter the house.",
      "Answer": "by"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It was a long walk, so he began moving slowly ________________ the town.",
      "Answer": "towards"
    },
    {
      "Question": "James‟' wife accused him _____________ cheating.",
      "Answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ are several new houses on his street.",
      "Answer": "There"
    },
    {
      "Question": "________ any food in the house.",
      "Answer": "There isn‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ is a great sweater. I like the colour.",
      "Answer": "This"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Today is our ________ anniversary. They are in Paris to celebrate.",
      "Answer": "parents‟'"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This shop is having a sale. All _______ clothing is 50 per cent off.",
      "Answer": "women‟s's"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you like the dark blue jacket? -______________________.",
      "Answer": "No, but I like the brown one"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ is Charlie.",
      "Answer": "My dog‟s's name"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This question is _____ difficult for me.",
      "Answer": "too"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This car is more _____ than that one.",
      "Answer": "modern"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mt. Everest is _____ than Mt Fuji.",
      "Answer": "higher"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Bobis ______ thanMike.",
      "Answer": "moreknowledgeable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Michael Jordan is the _______ basketball player.",
      "Answer": "best"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This is the ______ movie I've ever seen.",
      "Answer": "mostboring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tom _________ coffee. He doesn‟t't like it.",
      "Answer": "doesn‟t't drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He _______ tennis when he broke his wrist.",
      "Answer": "was playing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Were there any letters today? - No, the postman _______ yet",
      "Answer": "hasn‟t't come"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This record-shop _____ be a book-shop a few years ago.",
      "Answer": "usedto"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He arrived _____ you were asleep.",
      "Answer": "while"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\"Have you ever been to France?\" \"Yes, I _____ there last August.\"",
      "Answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It'sMrSmith, _____?",
      "Answer": "isn'tit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I usually wear skirts, but today I _____ trousers.",
      "Answer": "amwearing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She hasn't written to me _____ we met last time.",
      "Answer": "since"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You look really hot. _____________?",
      "Answer": "Have you been running"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When I arrived at the airport, the plane _________.",
      "Answer": "had already left"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This problem _______ by your brother yesterday.",
      "Answer": "was solved"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My sister ______ out to the cinema with me.",
      "Answer": "is going"
    },
    {
      "Question": "These boys ______ the missing child.",
      "Answer": "found"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The eclipse ________ by everybody.",
      "Answer": "will be seen"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I told him ____ do it.",
      "Answer": "notto"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I askedher________.",
      "Answer": "whattheanswerwas"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hesaid._________.",
      "Answer": "hewentdowntown the day before"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hesaid___________.",
      "Answer": "he would study for the exam"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Joanasked _________.",
      "Answer": "iftherewascoffee"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She took accounting courses _______ for her business.",
      "Answer": "to prepare"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Last year she succeeded in ______ a loan from the bank.",
      "Answer": "getting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ experience is important so we all told her to keep trying.",
      "Answer": "Getting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ira has stopped _______ coffee because it was making her jumpy",
      "Answer": "drinking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Thank you for your letter. I look forward ________ you next week.",
      "Answer": "to meeting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The road repairs ___________ out on the motorway might delay traffic.",
      "Answer": "carried"
    },
    {
      "Question": "________ all traces of his crime, the criminal left the building.",
      "Answer": "Havingremoved"
    },
    {
      "Question": "____________ TV, she fell asleep.",
      "Answer": "Watching"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ a foreigner, she needs a visa to stay in this country.",
      "Answer": "Being"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ his address I couldn't contact him.",
      "Answer": "Notknowing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I don‟t't want ______ to stay.",
      "Answer": "him"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟d'd like this book __________.",
      "Answer": "to be published"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We told jokes and it made time ________.",
      "Answer": "pass"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Nobody noticed Julie ________ the house.",
      "Answer": "leave"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mother wanted ________ to wash up.",
      "Answer": "me"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He seems _______ a lot.",
      "Answer": "to be reading"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She hoped ______ by her friends.",
      "Answer": "to be helped"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She is not likely _______ her opinion.",
      "Answer": "to change"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I felt Nick ______ his hand on my shoulder.",
      "Answer": "put"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The bag is not likely ________.",
      "Answer": "tohavebeenstolen"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Mr. Hertel ______ by plane, he orders a special meal.",
      "Answer": "travels"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Unless we _______ a service station in the next five minutes, we are going to run out of gas.",
      "Answer": "find"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If I ______ Tom, I‟d'd start looking for a new job.",
      "Answer": "were"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The garage is a mess. I wish we _____ more time to clean it out.",
      "Answer": "had"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Michael ___________ what he said if he hadn‟t't been hurt and angry",
      "Answer": "wouldn‟t't have said"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ I hadn‟t't lost my appointment book.",
      "Answer": "If only"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm so hungry. I feel ______ I could eat a horse.",
      "Answer": "as if"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Virginia, _______ is said to be quite beautiful, is the home of many senators and representatives now.",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "San Francisco, America's most romantic city, has always been a haven for the artists and writers ______ have left at least part of their hearts there.",
      "Answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Martin Stevenson, ______ children I have been looking after since i started the university in London, is my history professor.",
      "Answer": "whose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Are you going swimming? ___ I come with you, please?",
      "Answer": "Can"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I'm not going to pay five pounds for a coffee. You ____ be joking!",
      "Answer": "must"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It _____ rain, so take an umbrella.",
      "Answer": "might"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They left London at three o'clock so they ______ be here by now",
      "Answer": "should"
    },
    {
      "Question": "His wife returned the sweater he bought her to the store. She____",
      "Answer": "can'thavelikedit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Choose the correct word order:",
      "Answer": "There is a snake in the well."
    },
    {
      "Question": "Choose the correct word order:",
      "Answer": "The cup was full of hot water."
    },
    {
      "Question": "There are too many chairs around that table, ________?",
      "Answer": "aren‟t't there"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you know ______ language is spoken in Kenya?",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I have no idea _____________.",
      "Answer": "where she is"
    },
    {
      "Question": "One child is here and the other _____ are outdoors",
      "Answer": "children"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lookat all these ________ !",
      "Answer": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This foot of the chair is broken, but the other _____ are fine",
      "Answer": "feet"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ have you got in the bank? Is it enough to buy a house?",
      "Answer": "How much money"
    },
    {
      "Question": "On Saturday, my friend Paul went fishing and he caught ________",
      "Answer": "three fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Sally won the lottery, she pinched _______ to make sure she wasn't dreaming.",
      "Answer": "herself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ in the village went to the party but ________ enjoyed it very much.",
      "Answer": "Everyone / nobody"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I don't like this chair. I like ___________ one over there",
      "Answer": "that"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Don't do it like that. Do it like ___________.",
      "Answer": "this"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We all told the boss that we wanted to have ______ salaries paid in advance but he just ignored _______.",
      "Answer": "his / we"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lupe asked, “How often do you eat cereal for breakfast?” Carlos replied, “_____”",
      "Answer": "Ever"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Kristina is absent every Monday. She ______ to class",
      "Answer": "comes never"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Gustavo almost never comes to class on time. He _______ almost always late.",
      "Answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She was riding her bike _______.",
      "Answer": "careful"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The train was very ______.",
      "Answer": "fast"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Judy goes to ______ by bus.",
      "Answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "Question": "While I was in hospital, they gave me _______.",
      "Answer": "an X-ray"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Did you learn to play _______ when you were a child?",
      "Answer": "the violin"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The space capsule came down in ______ Pacific",
      "Answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What _____ clever children you have.",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The woman was getting _____ the car.",
      "Answer": "out of"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The new manager takes over _____ two weeks‟' time.",
      "Answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I saw a really funny program ________ television",
      "Answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Could you let me know _____ Friday at the latest?",
      "Answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We could see the balloon high _____ the town.",
      "Answer": "above"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ a man in the garden?",
      "Answer": "Is there"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In this glass _____ some milk.",
      "Answer": "there is"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In our class we have students from Italy, Spain and Saudi Arabia but _________ no students from France.",
      "Answer": "thereare"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When I was at school _____________ any computers. But now every school has many computers.",
      "Answer": "thereweren't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Think of me _____ I am away.",
      "Answer": "while"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟l'll love you _____ I die.",
      "Answer": "until"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I fell in love _____ we met.",
      "Answer": "as soon as"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They put video cameras in shops _______ stop people from stealing.",
      "Answer": "in order to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Detective stories are ________ than algebra.",
      "Answer": "more interesting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They‟v've got lost of fans. They are _______ team in the country!",
      "Answer": "the most popular"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You needn‟t't go yet. You can stay a bit _______.",
      "Answer": "longer"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There are lots of break-ins. They happen _______ nowadays.",
      "Answer": "more often"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm not used to country walks. How much ______ is it?",
      "Answer": "further"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Our new car is _____ so it uses _____ petrol.",
      "Answer": "smaller, less"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mary usually has a ______ before going to school",
      "Answer": "glass of milk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "__________ to talk makes him unlike any other animal",
      "Answer": "Man‟s's ability"
    },
    {
      "Question": "__________ car has been broken",
      "Answer": "My mother-in-law‟s's"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_________ room is always tidy",
      "Answer": "My mother and father‟s's"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This clock ____ in ",
      "Answer": "was made"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They will ________ this car soon",
      "Answer": "buy"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Claire arrived, Henry _________ up and down",
      "Answer": "was walking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When the students _________ the experiment, they wrote a report on it",
      "Answer": "had done"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sorry, I can‟t't stop now. I ________ to an important meeting",
      "Answer": "am going"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Please, don‟t't hurry. We_________ for you.",
      "Answer": "will wait"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Well, I‟d'd better hurry. My lesson ____ in half an hour",
      "Answer": "starts"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The story was written _______ Agatha Christie.",
      "Answer": "by"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Nigel‟s's had his passport ___________.",
      "Answer": "stolen"
    },
    {
      "Question": "These products __________.",
      "Answer": "have to be tested"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is this your CD? – No, it‟s's not mine, I ______ it ______ to Peter",
      "Answer": "think, belongs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We __________ the holiday very much.",
      "Answer": "enjoyed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I called my friend in New York yesterday and he said that it _____ there",
      "Answer": "was raining"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I wonder _____ those shoes are on sale yet.",
      "Answer": "whether"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I told you ______ play with matches, didn‟t't I?",
      "Answer": "not to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My friend _____ she liked her new flat.",
      "Answer": "said"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The last time I saw Mary, she was very happy. She explained that she‟d'd got married _____ week.",
      "Answer": "the previous"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_________ his breakfast, he felt much better.",
      "Answer": "Having finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "__________ in the story, he ignored everyone around him",
      "Answer": "Interested"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_________ a politician, he always wore suits to work",
      "Answer": "Being"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We saw a panda _______ some leaves.",
      "Answer": "eating"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ in her best clothes she looked gorgeous.",
      "Answer": "Dressed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I really enjoy ___________",
      "Answer": "skating"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you still work for that company? No, I gave up _____ there a month ago.",
      "Answer": "working"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He refused ______ there with me",
      "Answer": "to go"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Jenny wants ______ us this winter",
      "Answer": "to visit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I would like ______ this beautiful dress on",
      "Answer": "to try"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Many books _____ to be published in our country every year.",
      "Answer": "are known"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I saw her ________ into that building",
      "Answer": "came"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He made me ______ the window",
      "Answer": "close"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The man was seen ______ his coat",
      "Answer": "taking off"
    },
    {
      "Question": "His invention _______ to be of great importance",
      "Answer": "is considered"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The day ______ John rang Jenny was really busy",
      "Answer": "when"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The woman _______ dog bit a child was very aggressive",
      "Answer": "whose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The talk ______ Jessy gave at the conference was very interesting",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The school _____ I used to study in is closed now.",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The man ______ has just crossed the street is my friend",
      "Answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If I _______ the money, I would have given you a good present",
      "Answer": "had had"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If I ______ to bed late, I would have a headache in the morning",
      "Answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If you tell me the instructions, I _______ them",
      "Answer": "will follow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If I had his address, I ______ him a letter",
      "Answer": "would write"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If Paul had taken part in the game, we ____________",
      "Answer": "would have won"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The baby‟s's asleep. We ______ make noise",
      "Answer": "mustn‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I can do it myself. You _________ help me",
      "Answer": "don‟t't have to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "________ help you with this task? – Oh, thank you",
      "Answer": "Shall I"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I _______ dance well when I was young",
      "Answer": "could"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You ________ very tired after spending 12 hours driving",
      "Answer": "must have been"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Why don‟t't you talk to Helen? – We have fallen ______",
      "Answer": "out"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Please, turn that music _____, I can‟t't hear myself think",
      "Answer": "down"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I can‟t't really tell you anything now, it doesn‟t't depend _____ me",
      "Answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The woman accused me _____ stealing her bag but I denied doing so",
      "Answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We really look forward ______ seeing you again",
      "Answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There are _____ parks or gardens in the city center",
      "Answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Would you like some tea? – Yes, I ______.",
      "Answer": "would"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Why _____ we sit on the balcony? – Good idea",
      "Answer": "don‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who _____ some ice-cream?",
      "Answer": "wants"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I can come here whenever I want, _____ I?",
      "Answer": "can‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Let me give you ______",
      "Answer": "a piece of advice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The contents of the boxes ______ thrown away",
      "Answer": "was"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The police ______ questioning the men",
      "Answer": "are"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I have never seen so many ______ in my life",
      "Answer": "deer"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can we have two ______, please?",
      "Answer": "coffees"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which should we choose? – I don‟t't mind, pick _____ you like",
      "Answer": "any"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Would you mind waiting ______ minutes?",
      "Answer": "a few"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mike has failed his test. Now he feels sorry for ______",
      "Answer": "himself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Her parents were in Malaya. So were ________",
      "Answer": "mine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The cat caught _____ tail in the door.",
      "Answer": "its"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They always defend _____. If you blame one, the other will spring to her aid.",
      "Answer": "oneanother"
    },
    {
      "Question": "No one can find Alice and David ______",
      "Answer": "anywhere"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The shop doesn‟t't sell new shoes, it only sells old _____",
      "Answer": "ones"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Her hair is so ________ – like a baby‟s's hair",
      "Answer": "soft"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I am not _______ today",
      "Answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Botanists are ______ in plants",
      "Answer": "interested"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You speak very _____ Japanese",
      "Answer": "good"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I am sorry but you are _______ wrong",
      "Answer": "completely"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Anna _______ so pessimistic",
      "Answer": "is always"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We went on a boat trip on _____ Lake Superior",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What‟s's for dinner? ______ same as yesterday",
      "Answer": "The"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What _____ strange house!",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It happened in _____ evening last summer",
      "Answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My sister is married to ______ plumber",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you like ________ Italian food?",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When we entered ______ the room everyone stopped talking",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Are you accusing me ______?",
      "Answer": "of lying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can you look ____ the children tomorrow?",
      "Answer": "after"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The report will be ready _____ Wednesday ____ 5 o‟c'clock",
      "Answer": "on, at"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We drove _____ that building, but we didn‟t't go inside",
      "Answer": "past"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The weather is _____ today",
      "Answer": "better"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Peter is ______ runner in the team",
      "Answer": "the fastest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ I learn, ______ I forget",
      "Answer": "The more, the more"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Nick‟s's got three brothers. Mark‟s's _______",
      "Answer": "the eldest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This film is _____ I have ever seen",
      "Answer": "the worst"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Everything was ok ______ we started talking about holidays",
      "Answer": "until"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_______ we did our best, we didn‟t't manage to finish the task in time",
      "Answer": "Although"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We need to get home before it ________ dark",
      "Answer": "gets"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You look _____ you‟v've seen a ghost",
      "Answer": "as if"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You can come with me ________ you behave",
      "Answer": "unless"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“He‟s's a great artist”. – “I ________",
      "Answer": "agree"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My sister ______ you",
      "Answer": "looks like"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I think it ________ $3000 to rebuild the house",
      "Answer": "will cost"
    },
    {
      "Question": "By the time they come, we _________ everything",
      "Answer": "will have finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "These plans _________ discussed at the meeting next week",
      "Answer": "are going to be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I looked out of the window. A strange man _______ in the garden",
      "Answer": "was standing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Everybody _____ that she was unhappy",
      "Answer": "knew"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He couldn‟t't change his clothes in the hotel because he ______ his luggage",
      "Answer": "had lost"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How long ________ in this town?",
      "Answer": "have you been living"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I _______ a new job",
      "Answer": "have been offered"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Your car will be ready soon. It ______ now",
      "Answer": "is being repaired"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The work ______ tomorrow",
      "Answer": "will be finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "These computers ______ in Korea",
      "Answer": "are made"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This project __________ by the time you come next month",
      "Answer": "will have been completed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When I get home I ______ 1000 kilometers",
      "Answer": "will have driven"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I asked ________",
      "Answer": "where my gloves were"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She asked him __________",
      "Answer": "whether he would like a drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I knew ___ figures ______ right",
      "Answer": "those, couldn‟t't be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He ordered me ______",
      "Answer": "not to stay"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He ______ me that he ______ me",
      "Answer": "told, loved"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The old man was walking along the street ______ to himself",
      "Answer": "talking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ an engineer, he ought to know how machine works",
      "Answer": "Being"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ the whole night out, he finally arrived home",
      "Answer": "Having spent"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Dogs often feel ______ during fireworks",
      "Answer": "frightened"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I think that snowy days in winter are ______",
      "Answer": "depressing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I don‟t't like ______ about my family",
      "Answer": "to be asked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You should _____ us you were in London",
      "Answer": "tell"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Their house is hard ______",
      "Answer": "to find"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She‟s's strange but you can‟t't help _____ her",
      "Answer": "liking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I can remember ______ the light off",
      "Answer": "switching"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I watched the children ____ with a ball",
      "Answer": "playing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My teacher makes me _____ hard",
      "Answer": "study"
    },
    {
      "Question": "They expected him ________ by the police",
      "Answer": "to be caught"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Parents usually expect ______ children to behave",
      "Answer": "their"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He seemed ______ me",
      "Answer": "to know"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He is known _______ English for 5 years",
      "Answer": "to have been studying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟l'll be very happy if I _____ the exam",
      "Answer": "pass"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I would put on a sweater if I _____ you",
      "Answer": "were"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If police hadn‟t't stopped us, things ________ all right",
      "Answer": "would have been"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I don‟t't want to call Mary. I‟d'd rather you ______ her",
      "Answer": "phoned"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It‟s's time we ____ home",
      "Answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Somebody won‟t't stop talking. If only they _____ talking",
      "Answer": "would stop"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I am bad at sports. I wish I ______ good at it",
      "Answer": "were"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I won‟t't go to New York unless you ______ with me",
      "Answer": "come"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I would have seen Alex, If I ______ to London",
      "Answer": "had gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The sofa _____ we bought last year looks old",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The money ______ is lying on the table is your change",
      "Answer": "that"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The day _____ I was born on was very windy and cold",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The village,____ we were staying in last year, was very beautiful",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The girl, ____ I gave your umbrella, looked very cold",
      "Answer": "whom"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I am not sure but I ______ made a mistake in my yesterday‟s's test",
      "Answer": "may have"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Her office is locked. She _____ gone home",
      "Answer": "must have"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ tell me the time?",
      "Answer": "Could you"
    },
    {
      "Question": "That _____ Angela. She is away on holiday now",
      "Answer": "can‟t't be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You _______ get a visa to go from England to Scotland",
      "Answer": "don‟t't have to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Excuse me, but ______ this train stop at Craydon?",
      "Answer": "does"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Never _______ to listen to so many boring people!",
      "Answer": "had I"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She explained ______ that it was about communication between people",
      "Answer": "to us"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He says he needs a knife ______ scissors to open that packet",
      "Answer": "and"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The team all wanted coffee so I made ______",
      "Answer": "them some"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What‟s's the matter? – You‟v've got ______ on your shirt",
      "Answer": "some eggs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ninety kilos _____ too heavy for me to lift",
      "Answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The news ______ worse than I expected",
      "Answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The police ________ people to stay at home after it gets dark",
      "Answer": "have warned"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you eat _________?",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You and I work together. _______ are a good team",
      "Answer": "We"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I haven‟t't met Mark yet. Is _____ here? – That‟s's ____ over there",
      "Answer": "he, him"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Thailand is quite unusual. _____ has never been ruled by another country",
      "Answer": "It"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mary bought a book and taught ______ to play the guitar",
      "Answer": "herself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hillary and Jenny write to ______ every week",
      "Answer": "each other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I was looking for a __________ spoon",
      "Answer": "little plastic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I left the book on the table. ______, someone has stolen it",
      "Answer": "Presumably"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I know I‟m'm _____ in my forties, but I _____ imagined I would need glasses",
      "Answer": "already, never"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm waiting here but Sandra has ______ left",
      "Answer": "already"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The ____ you wait, the ____ you are to miss the _____ bargains on sale",
      "Answer": "longer, more likely, best"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She‟s's interested in _____ art and _____ African history",
      "Answer": "--,--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My younger sister is ______ doctor",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What _____ great day!",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When I go to _____ Paris, I want to see ____ Eiffel Tower",
      "Answer": "--, the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ mount Everest is very high",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We‟r're not going away _____ Easter",
      "Answer": "at"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The city is beautiful ____ May",
      "Answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She was standing _____ a crowd of children",
      "Answer": "among"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I arrived _____ the station at six.",
      "Answer": "at"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I arrived ____ London at five",
      "Answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Don‟t't spend your money _____ that car, it‟s's not worth it",
      "Answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This book belongs ____ me",
      "Answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My friends are not very interested _____ history",
      "Answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm responsible _____ finance",
      "Answer": "for"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ my opinion this book is a waste of time",
      "Answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My headache was getting _____ so I went home",
      "Answer": "worse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We‟v've got ____ money than our friends but we are _____",
      "Answer": "less, happier"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ he gets, _____ he looks like his father",
      "Answer": "The older, the more"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The book was _____ boring that I stopped reading it",
      "Answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Peter is _____ student in our class",
      "Answer": "the best"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Vegetarians are people who ________ meat",
      "Answer": "don‟t't eat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Let‟s's go home. It ______ late",
      "Answer": "is getting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My friend ______ me next week. He‟s's already bought the tickets",
      "Answer": "is visiting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I ______ the cups. You can dry them",
      "Answer": "will wash"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We ______ the report by 5 o‟c'clock",
      "Answer": "will have finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Don‟t't call me at 5, I ________ then",
      "Answer": "will be having"
    },
    {
      "Question": "At six o‟c'clock I ______ a wonderful dream but then the alarm ____",
      "Answer": "was having, went off"
    },
    {
      "Question": "After we got home, grandma ______ us some tea",
      "Answer": "made"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He ______ a book while I ______ the house",
      "Answer": "was reading, was cleaning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "____ the baby ______ anything to eat yet?",
      "Answer": "Has, had"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It _________ all day today",
      "Answer": "has been raining"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How long _______ Chris?",
      "Answer": "Have you known"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When she ______ six pairs of shoes, she _____ she liked the first pair best",
      "Answer": "had tried, decided"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It wasn‟t't the first time they _______ how it worked",
      "Answer": "had been explained"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Soup _______ with a spoon",
      "Answer": "is eaten"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Town Hall ________",
      "Answer": "has just been rebuilt"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This door _________",
      "Answer": "can‟t't be opened"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Your room ________ at the moment, it will be ready soon",
      "Answer": "is being cleaned"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The work _______ tomorrow",
      "Answer": "will be finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“Invisible” means ________",
      "Answer": "can‟t't be seen"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She said that she ____ me ______",
      "Answer": "would see, the day after"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She asked me _____ I liked it there",
      "Answer": "whether"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He told me that his uncle _____",
      "Answer": "had died the previous week"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She ______ she was tired",
      "Answer": "said"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She asked me _______ the door",
      "Answer": "not to close"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I asked her _____________",
      "Answer": "what Peter‟s's address was"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Jane‟s's fed up with _____",
      "Answer": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Their house is easy _______",
      "Answer": "to find"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm just not capable ________",
      "Answer": "of drawing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We all agreed ______ Andy",
      "Answer": "to help"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I think I should stop ______ chocolate; it‟s's not good for my health",
      "Answer": "eating"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I remember ______ my keys on the table, but they are not there any more",
      "Answer": "putting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Radium is said ______ very radioactive",
      "Answer": "to be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "For a long time the atom _________ to be invisible",
      "Answer": "was thought"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My friend is sure _______ soon",
      "Answer": "to be back"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Shhh! I hear the baby ___________",
      "Answer": "crying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I heard my mum ______ me",
      "Answer": "call"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I know ______ to be a good student",
      "Answer": "him"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Rainy weather makes people _____ sad",
      "Answer": "feel"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟v've had a very ______ day. It‟s's my birthday!",
      "Answer": "exciting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "We all were very ________ with the party",
      "Answer": "disappointed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "________ the letter he posted it",
      "Answer": "Having written"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The result _____ during the experiment is very important",
      "Answer": "obtained"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ the test, he made only one mistake",
      "Answer": "Doing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A fish ______ out of the water cannot live",
      "Answer": "taken"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Although it was expensive, _____ he bought it",
      "Answer": "--"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He can neither sing _____play anything",
      "Answer": "nor"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I _____ you if we move",
      "Answer": "will miss"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The kitchen would look better if we ____ red curtains",
      "Answer": "had"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If it ______ so cold, I would tidy up in the garden",
      "Answer": "weren‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The team ______ if the player hadn‟t't broken his leg",
      "Answer": "would have won"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I know a shop _____ sells good coffee",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A lot of people _____ I know want to move to some other country",
      "Answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He was born on the day _____ the war started",
      "Answer": "when"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A good parent is one ______ children are happy",
      "Answer": "whose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Books ____ disappear in 50 years",
      "Answer": "may"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You _____ three apples, there were only two in the fridge",
      "Answer": "couldn‟t't have taken"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I ______ him about it, he already knew the truth",
      "Answer": "needn‟t't have told"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I would love to _____ travel more",
      "Answer": "be able to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He _____ to work harder",
      "Answer": "ought"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ our friends at the pizzeria last night",
      "Answer": "We met"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Have you had a hard week? You _____ this evening",
      "Answer": "seem tired"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The recent conflict has ____ of the problems in the country",
      "Answer": "made people aware"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The manager promised ____ a pay rise if we worked extra hours for a while",
      "Answer": "us all"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can you throw ____ ? I‟l'll get the things from the boot",
      "Answer": "me the car keys"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She has two young ____ so she‟s's always tired!",
      "Answer": "babies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The police _____ questions about the bank robbery",
      "Answer": "are asking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you have suitable ____ for this job?",
      "Answer": "experience"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Excuse me. Is there _____ near here?",
      "Answer": "an art gallery"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There was an interesting ____ on the radio this morning",
      "Answer": "items of news"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mr Green is ____ English teacher",
      "Answer": "our"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ are fifteen students in my class",
      "Answer": "There"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It‟s's my _____ computer",
      "Answer": "parents‟'"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Those bags are _______",
      "Answer": "theirs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This is _____ house",
      "Answer": "Tom‟s's"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can you please tell me what ____ is?",
      "Answer": "your phone number"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can you hear _____ ?",
      "Answer": "me"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where are my sunglasses? – Here _____ are.",
      "Answer": "they"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you think this is _____ ?",
      "Answer": "a difficult exercise"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Dave‟s's wearing a _____ striped shirt",
      "Answer": "blue and white"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I can‟t't wait for my next holiday. I‟m'm really ___ about it!",
      "Answer": "excited"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I love detective novels. I think they are _____ interesting",
      "Answer": "really"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I don‟t't like the sea because I can‟t't swim _____",
      "Answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I ____ football matches on TV",
      "Answer": "hardly ever watch"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you know why the repairman _____ ?",
      "Answer": "did not come yesterday"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I always learn a lot of things at ____ school",
      "Answer": "–"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I hate ____ exams",
      "Answer": "–"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The interesting thing about _____ Romans is all the roads they built in Britain",
      "Answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What ____ strange girl!",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "Question": "____ Tate Gallery is the main modern art museum in London",
      "Answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The hotel is closed for repairs ____ the end of February",
      "Answer": "until"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Have you got enough cash? – No, I‟l'll pay ____ credit card",
      "Answer": "by"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The film is good but there‟s's a lot of violence ____ the end",
      "Answer": "at"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The plane was due to arrive at 15 and it landed right _____ time",
      "Answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I still haven‟t't heard anything from the interview I had ____ Monday",
      "Answer": "last"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The blue car is ____ than the red one",
      "Answer": "faster"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mona Lisa is one of _____ paintings in the museum",
      "Answer": "most beautiful"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Bob is ____ than Mike",
      "Answer": "more knowledgeable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Some governments are _____ than others",
      "Answer": "worse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A blue whale is the ____ animal in the world",
      "Answer": "heaviest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Moscow is a long way away but Ulan Butur is even _______",
      "Answer": "farther"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This time tomorrow some of the people in this room ____ to their home countries",
      "Answer": "will be travelling"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Augusto couldn‟t't open the classroom door because one of the other students ____ if from the inside",
      "Answer": "had locked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Every day, even when it‟s's raining heavily, Henry ___ for an early morning run before eating breakfast",
      "Answer": "goes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "At the moment, _____ an exercise in order to review the English verb tenses that I have learned",
      "Answer": "I‟m'm doing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Before people landed on the Moon in 1969, some people ____ that the moon was made of cheese",
      "Answer": "had believed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "By Christmas, all of the students in our class _____ to their countries",
      "Answer": "will have returned"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This is Javi‟s's last week at the school so _____ Goodbye to all of his new friends for the last three days",
      "Answer": "he‟s's been saying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm sorry I can‟t't come to your party tomorrow night. ____ dinner with Christina and Samara. Maybe I can come along afterwards",
      "Answer": "I‟m'm having"
    },
    {
      "Question": "So far, during her time at International House Bristol, Tchior ____ to six pancake parties and fifteen barbecues",
      "Answer": "has come"
    },
    {
      "Question": "At six o‟c'clock this morning most of us were asleep in bed. But Atheer ____ for today‟s's grammar",
      "Answer": "was studying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This is the second to last question in this set of questions. In two minutes‟' time you ____ and then you will find out your score",
      "Answer": "will have finished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Elisabetta _____ for her morning lesson, the teacher was collecting the homework from the other students",
      "Answer": "arrived"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I have to go to work by taxi because my car ____ at the garage",
      "Answer": "is being repaired"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Customers are asked to make sure that they ____ the right change before leaving the shop",
      "Answer": "have been given"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This house ____ in 1970 by my grandfather",
      "Answer": "was built"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The robbers _____ by the police",
      "Answer": "have been arrested"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The students ____ to submit their reports by the end of this week",
      "Answer": "are asked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The teacher ____ the student for lying",
      "Answer": "punished"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The inmates of the juvenile home ____ well by their caretakers",
      "Answer": "were not being treated"
    },
    {
      "Question": "As the patient could not walk he ___ home in a wheel chair",
      "Answer": "was carried"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I told him ____ do it",
      "Answer": "not to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He asked us ___ show our passports",
      "Answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Do you play chess?",
      "Answer": "He asked me if I played chess"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Travel agent: “ I think the train will be on time.” – The travel agent said _____",
      "Answer": "that she thought the train would be on time"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Byron: “I can‟t't swim.” Byron said _____",
      "Answer": "he couldn‟t't swim"
    },
    {
      "Question": "For most people in the 21st century, it‟s's hard to imagine ____ without television",
      "Answer": "living"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If you have difficulty ____ all the questions on this page, you need to revise gerunds and infinitives again",
      "Answer": "completing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Because it was very cold in Classroom G, our teacher let us _____ coffee or hot chocolate into the room",
      "Answer": "bring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I‟m'm so forgetful. I keep leaving my house without ____ to lock the front door",
      "Answer": "remembering"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The road repairs _____ out on the motorway might delay traffic",
      "Answer": "carried"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ all traces of his crime, the criminal left the building",
      "Answer": "Having removed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "______ TV, she fell asleep",
      "Answer": "Watching"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ a foreigner, she needs a visa to stay in this country",
      "Answer": "Being"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ his address I couldn‟t't contact him",
      "Answer": "Not knowing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I saw her ____ into the building",
      "Answer": "coming"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I believed you _____ three mobile phones",
      "Answer": "to have"
    },
    {
      "Question": "He made me ____ the window",
      "Answer": "close"
    },
    {
      "Question": "I saw them _____ in the park",
      "Answer": "play"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She believes Mark _____ a good guy",
      "Answer": "to be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The president _____ the countries of Eastern Europe",
      "Answer": "is reported to be visiting"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hush! Do you feel ____ behind us? It is so frightening here",
      "Answer": "someone breathing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Jennie ____ a very smart and hard-working girl",
      "Answer": "is said to be"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is absolutely necessary _____ all the papers with him",
      "Answer": "that he brings"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mr Richards, ______ is a taxi driver, lives on the corner",
      "Answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Thank you very much for your e-mail _____ was very interesting",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Taylor has a new car, _____ is twice as big as his old one",
      "Answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The hotel _____ we stayed had recently been renovated",
      "Answer": "A and C are both possible"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A hammer is a tool _____ is used to knock nails into wood",
      "Answer": "that"
    },
    {
      "Question": "My friend, _____ doesn‟t't have a cell phone, suddenly knocked on the door last night",
      "Answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If you ____ maths at school, you would find commerce difficult to understand",
      "Answer": "didn‟t't learn"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If that was John, why _____ he stop and say hello?",
      "Answer": "didn‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Oil _____ if you pour it on water",
      "Answer": "floats"
    },
    {
      "Question": "She would have come if you _____ her",
      "Answer": "had invited"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If I _____ enough time tomorrow, I will come and see you",
      "Answer": "have got"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is it your birthday? You ______ have told me. I would have got you a present",
      "Answer": "should"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You _____ be joking! I‟m'm not going to lend him my new car",
      "Answer": "must"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_____ I have a quick word with you Brian? It‟s's nothing serious",
      "Answer": "Could"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is ten pounds enough for a taxi? – I _____ so. It‟s's less than two miles",
      "Answer": "should"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You _____ smoke near children",
      "Answer": "shouldn‟t't"
    },
    {
      "Question": "34. Kids listened to the new teacher _______ we expected",
      "Answer": "B) more patiently than"
    },
    {
      "Question": "35. Cars are twice _______ they were a year ago",
      "Answer": "D) as expensive as"
    },
    {
      "Question": "36. I can't hear you. Can you speak _______?",
      "Answer": "B) louder"
    },
    {
      "Question": "37. Ben _______ to us since he changed his address",
      "Answer": "C) hasn't written"
    },
    {
      "Question": "38. Kevin hopes he _______ all over the world by that time",
      "Answer": "A) will have travelled"
    },
    {
      "Question": "39. When we go to Paris, we _______ the Eiffel Tower",
      "Answer": "A) will climb"
    },
    {
      "Question": "40. By the time Rick retires, he _______ for the same company for thirty years",
      "Answer": "C) will have worked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "41. Dad _______ to work by the time I woke up",
      "Answer": "C) had already gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "42. The bills _______ by Friday",
      "Answer": "D) will have been paid"
    },
    {
      "Question": "43. Computers _______ more and more efficient",
      "Answer": "C) are becoming"
    },
    {
      "Question": "44. These reports _______ two years ago",
      "Answer": "A) were published"
    },
    {
      "Question": "45. Mr. Johnson and his wife _______ Italian for three years now",
      "Answer": "D) have been learning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "46. My teeth _______ by the dentist tomorrow",
      "Answer": "B) will be checked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "47. The program _______ on Sunday",
      "Answer": "B) will be broadcast"
    },
    {
      "Question": "48. This time next week I _______ in the Highlands",
      "Answer": "C) will be walking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "49. Mary _______ to Singapore at three tomorrow morning",
      "Answer": "A) will be flying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "50. Nobody _______ harder than Tom does",
      "Answer": "D) works"
    },
    {
      "Question": "51. I always _______ computer things by mail order",
      "Answer": "B) buy"
    },
    {
      "Question": "52. The US President _______ for health reasons. He _______ his decision a few minutes ago",
      "Answer": "C) resigned, announced"
    },
    {
      "Question": "53. _______ any plans for the weekend? - Yes, I _______ visit my sister",
      "Answer": "A) Have you made, am going to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "54. My suggestions _______ at again now",
      "Answer": "A) are being laughed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "55. The project was very expensive. It _______ millions of pounds",
      "Answer": "B) cost"
    },
    {
      "Question": "56. The BBC World Service _______. It _______ all over the world",
      "Answer": "D) is well known, is listened to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "57. Paul _______ to Tina when I saw him",
      "Answer": "A) w'as talking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "58. Concord, the world's fastest passenger plane, _______ by France and Britain together",
      "Answer": "D) was developed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "59. Where _______? - In France",
      "Answer": "B) is champagne produced"
    },
    {
      "Question": "60. I've _______ to most countries in Europe, but I've never _______ to Russia",
      "Answer": "A) been, been"
    },
    {
      "Question": "61. Can I speak to Mr. Thompson, please? - I'm afraid he _______ out of the office",
      "Answer": "A) has just gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "62. Simon this week? - No, he _______ to Greece",
      "Answer": "B) Have you seen, has gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "63. The streets are wet _______?",
      "Answer": "D) Has it been raining"
    },
    {
      "Question": "64. Mark has borrowed our CDs. - Well, I hope he brings _______",
      "Answer": "C) them back"
    },
    {
      "Question": "65. What happened to the TV set? - A man came and took it _______",
      "Answer": "D) away"
    },
    {
      "Question": "66. A piece of cheese will keep _______ hunger for a time",
      "Answer": "A) off"
    },
    {
      "Question": "67. We began to work at 12 and went _______ till half-past one",
      "Answer": "D) on"
    },
    {
      "Question": "34. Kids listened to the new teacher _______ we expected",
      "Answer": "B) more patiently than"
    },
    {
      "Question": "35. Cars are twice _______ they were a year ago",
      "Answer": "D) as expensive as"
    },
    {
      "Question": "36. I can't hear you. Can you speak _______?",
      "Answer": "B) louder"
    },
    {
      "Question": "37. Ben _______ to us since he changed his address",
      "Answer": "C) hasn't written"
    },
    {
      "Question": "38. Kevin hopes he _______ all over the world by that time",
      "Answer": "A) will have travelled"
    },
    {
      "Question": "39. When we go to Paris, we _______ the Eiffel Tower",
      "Answer": "A) will climb"
    },
    {
      "Question": "40. By the time Rick retires, he _______ for the same company for thirty years",
      "Answer": "C) will have worked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "41. Dad _______ to work by the time I woke up",
      "Answer": "C) had already gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "42. The bills _______ by Friday",
      "Answer": "D) will have been paid"
    },
    {
      "Question": "43. Computers _______ more and more efficient",
      "Answer": "C) are becoming"
    },
    {
      "Question": "44. These reports _______ two years ago",
      "Answer": "A) were published"
    },
    {
      "Question": "45. Mr. Johnson and his wife _______ Italian for three years now",
      "Answer": "D) have been learning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "46. My teeth _______ by the dentist tomorrow",
      "Answer": "B) will be checked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "47. The program _______ on Sunday",
      "Answer": "B) will be broadcast"
    },
    {
      "Question": "48. This time next week I _______ in the Highlands",
      "Answer": "C) will be walking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "49. Mary _______ to Singapore at three tomorrow morning",
      "Answer": "A) will be flying"
    },
    {
      "Question": "50. Nobody _______ harder than Tom does",
      "Answer": "D) works"
    },
    {
      "Question": "51. I always _______ computer things by mail order",
      "Answer": "B) buy"
    },
    {
      "Question": "52. The US President _______ for health reasons. He _______ his decision a few minutes ago",
      "Answer": "C) resigned, announced"
    },
    {
      "Question": "53. _______ any plans for the weekend? - Yes, I _______ visit my sister",
      "Answer": "A) Have you made, am going to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "54. My suggestions _______ at again now",
      "Answer": "A) are being laughed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "55. The project was very expensive. It _______ millions of pounds",
      "Answer": "B) cost"
    },
    {
      "Question": "56. The BBC World Service _______. It _______ all over the world",
      "Answer": "D) is well known, is listened to"
    },
    {
      "Question": "57. Paul _______ to Tina when I saw him",
      "Answer": "A) w'as talking"
    },
    {
      "Question": "58. Concord, the world's fastest passenger plane, _______ by France and Britain together",
      "Answer": "D) was developed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "59. Where _______? - In France",
      "Answer": "B) is champagne produced"
    },
    {
      "Question": "60. I've _______ to most countries in Europe, but I've never _______ to Russia",
      "Answer": "A) been, been"
    },
    {
      "Question": "61. Can I speak to Mr. Thompson, please? - I'm afraid he _______ out of the office",
      "Answer": "A) has just gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "62. Simon this week? - No, he _______ to Greece",
      "Answer": "B) Have you seen, has gone"
    },
    {
      "Question": "63. The streets are wet _______?",
      "Answer": "D) Has it been raining"
    },
    {
      "Question": "64. Mark has borrowed our CDs. - Well, I hope he brings _______",
      "Answer": "C) them back"
    },
    {
      "Question": "65. What happened to the TV set? - A man came and took it _______",
      "Answer": "D) away"
    },
    {
      "Question": "66. A piece of cheese will keep _______ hunger for a time",
      "Answer": "A) off"
    },
    {
      "Question": "67. We began to work at 12 and went _______ till half-past one",
      "Answer": "D) on"
    }
  ]
}